{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "front": "Anaranjado",
      "back": "Orange",
      "id": 3,
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Verde",
      "back": "Green",
      "id": 34,
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Amarillo",
      "back": "Yellow",
      "id": 239,
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "lbztc0s4",
      "front": "el ni√±o",
      "back": "child",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "lbztio2l",
      "front": "la ciudad",
      "back": "city",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "ag4gag",
      "front": "la carro",
      "back": "car",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "lcksinnf",
      "front": "Pizza",
      "back": "Pie",
      "deckId": "lcks0h1t"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcksl5q2",
      "front": "Rojo",
      "back": "Red",
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckuj9b5",
      "front": "2",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": "lcks0h1t"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckvo9rc",
      "front": "1",
      "back": "2",
      "deckId": "lcks0h1t"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckvo9rd",
      "front": "43",
      "back": "5",
      "deckId": "lcks0h1t"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckwtsmu",
      "front": "Cheese",
      "back": "good",
      "deckId": "lcksozlv"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckwtsmv",
      "front": "olives",
      "back": "Great!",
      "deckId": "lcksozlv"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckwtsmw",
      "front": "calzone",
      "back": "lo-cal-cal-zone-zone",
      "deckId": "lcksozlv"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcl22mym",
      "front": "a",
      "back": "b",
      "deckId": "lcl22iu2"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcl2ucvl",
      "front": "calzone?",
      "back": "Yest!",
      "deckId": "lcksozlv"
    },
    {
      "id": "lclu3uhn",
      "front": "asdf",
      "back": "asdf",
      "deckId": "3"
    }
  ],
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Spanish Colors"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Spanish Vocabulary"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcks0h1t",
      "name": "asdf"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcksozlv",
      "name": "pizza"
    },
    {
      "id": "lckx8swv",
      "name": "empty deck"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcl22iu2",
      "name": "One card"
    },
    {
      "id": "lcl2ukzi",
      "name": "Booo"
    }
  ]
}